To give you an idea of how useful RNNs and LSTMs are let's take a sneak peek.
为了让你体会到循环神经网络和长短期记忆网络的强大 我们来先睹为快
The world's leading tech companies are all using RNNs and LSTMs in their applications.
全球领先科技公司都在他们的应用中使用循环神经网络和长短期记忆网络
Let's take a look at some of those.
我们来具体看一下
Speech recognition, where a sequence of data samples
语音识别 即从音频信号中提取数据样本的序列
extracted from an audio signal is continuously mapped to text.
可以连续映射到文本
Good examples are Google Assistant,
这方面的例子包括谷歌语音助手 (Google Assistant)
Apple's Siri, Amazon's Alexa,
苹果公司的 Siri 亚马逊的 Alexa
and Nuance's Dragon solutions.
和纽昂斯的 Dragon 解决方案
All of these use RNNs as a part of their speech recognition software.
这些应用使用循环神经网络作为他们语音识别软件的一部分内容
Time series predictions, where we predict traffic patterns
在时间序列预测中 我们预测特定道路的交通模式
on specific roads to help drivers optimize their driving paths,
可以帮助司机优化他们的驾驶路线
like they do in Waze,
如同 Waze 软件一样
or predicting what movie a consumer will want to watch next,
或者预测消费者接下来想看的电影是什么
like they do in Netflix.
如同 Netflix 软件一样
Predicting stock price movements based on historical patterns
根据股票涨跌的历史模式和其他
of stock movements and potentially other market conditions,
随着时间变化的潜在市场因素
that change over time.
预测股价的涨跌
This is practiced by most quantitive hedge funds.
这是大多数量化对冲基金的工作
Natural Language Processing or NLP in short,
自然语言处理 简称 NLP
such as machine translation used by Google or Salesforce for example.
如谷歌或 Salesforce 使用的机器翻译
Question answering like Google Analytics,
谷歌分析 (Google Analytics) 的答题功能
if you've got a question about your app,
如果对自己的 app 有疑问
you'll soon be able to ask Google Analytics directly.
你可以直接向谷歌分析进行提问
Have you heard of chatbots?
你听说过聊天机器人 (chatbots) 吗？
Many companies such as Google, Baidu, and,
谷歌 百度和 Slack 等许多公司
Slack are using RNNs to drive
使用循环神经网络
their Natural Language Processing engines for such applications.
为这些应用提供自然语言处理的驱动引擎
And of course, there are many other NLP applications.
当然还有其他自然语言处理的许多应用
The last application we will focus on is gesture recognition,
我们关注的最后一个应用是手势识别
where we observe a sequence of video frames to determine which gesture the user has made.
其中我们观察一系列视频帧 确定使用者做出的手势
For example, waiving your right arm or swinging it.
例如挥动右臂或左右摆动
Here are a few gesture recognition technology companies
这是几个手势识别科技公司
and companies that are applying gesture recognition to their products.
这些公司已经把手势识别应用到自己的产品中